{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Organisms can synthesize ATP by oxidative phosphorylation when they", "opta": "ferment", "optb": "oxidize glucose to pyruvate", "optc": "pass electrons from the oxidation of chlorophyll through an electron transport system", "optd": "pass electrons to oxygen through an electron transport system containing cytochromes", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many molecules of carbon dioxide will be given off during ten turns of the Krebs cycle?", "opta": "10", "optb": "20", "optc": "30", "optd": "40", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In cellular metabolism, O2 is used", "opta": "to provide electrons for photophosphorylation", "optb": "in glycolysis", "optc": "as a terminal electron acceptor", "optd": "in the Krebs cycle", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In glycolysis, ATP is created by", "opta": "photophosphorylation", "optb": "the chemiosmotic mechanism", "optc": "substrate level phosphorylation", "optd": "the pentose phosphate pathway", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Suppose a eukaryotic cell had a mutation that prevented the production of cytochrome c. As a result of this mutation, which of the following processes would not occur?", "opta": "Cellular respiration", "optb": "Photosynthesis", "optc": "Mitosis", "optd": "Cell wall synthesis", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following best explains about the usefulness of the production of ethanol in yeast cells under anaerobic conditions?", "opta": "Ethanol keeps the electron transport system functioning", "optb": "Yeast would be unable to activate the enzymes of the Krebs cycle without ethanol", "optc": "The process generates oxygen, which is required for glycolysis", "optd": "The process regenerates NAD+, which is required for glycolysis", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The final electron acceptor in the electron transport chain is", "opta": "CoQ", "optb": "a cytochrome", "optc": "FMN", "optd": "oxygen", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The amount of energy (cal/mole) in an ATP molecule produced by a cell from glucose by fermentation is", "opta": "greater than aerobic metabolism", "optb": "less than aerobic metabolism", "optc": "exactly or approximately equal to aerobic metabolism", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The enzymes for glycolysis are located", "opta": "on the inner surface of the cell membrane", "optb": "on the inner membrane of the mitochondrion", "optc": "on the outer membrane of the chloroplast", "optd": "in the cytoplasm", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Glucose can be broken down to pyruvate by", "opta": "Entner-Doudoroff pathway", "optb": "tricarboxylic acid cycle", "optc": "both (a) and (b)", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In lactic acid fermentation, the final electron acceptor would be", "opta": "fructose", "optb": "pyruvate", "optc": "glucose", "optd": "acetyl-CoA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The amount of ATP that can be obtained by complete oxidation of a glucose by a bacterium is", "opta": "greater than by a yeast cell", "optb": "lesser than by a yeast cell", "optc": "exactly or approximately equal to by a yeast cell", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is accomplished in chemiosmosis?", "opta": "The oxidation of ATP", "optb": "The oxidation of water", "optc": "The oxidation of NADH", "optd": "The oxidation of CO2", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A yeast or fungal cell produces how many net ATP molecules per molecule of glucose when completely oxidized?", "opta": "32", "optb": "34", "optc": "36", "optd": "38", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Before most molecules can enter the Krebs citric acid cycle, they must be converted to", "opta": "citric acid", "optb": "oxaloacetic acid", "optc": "NADH or FADH", "optd": "acetyl-CoA", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many oxygen molecules are required in the fermentation of one molecule of glucose to ethanol and CO2?", "opta": "0", "optb": "1", "optc": "2", "optd": "36", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Most bacterial fermentations yield how many net ATP molecules per molecule of glucose?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "4", "optd": "6", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The amount of ATP produced by a cell from glucose when metabolizing it by fermentation means is", "opta": "greater than by aerobic metabolism", "optb": "lesser than by aerobic metabolism", "optc": "exactly or approximately equal to by aerobic metabolism", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is produced in the greatest numbers during one turn of the Krebs cycle?", "opta": "NADH", "optb": "Acetyl-CoA", "optc": "FADH2", "optd": "ATP", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Aerobic respiration differs from anaerobic respiration in which of the following respects?", "opta": "Anaerobic respiration is glycolysis", "optb": "Aerobic respiration requires the electron transport chain", "optc": "The final electron acceptors are different", "optd": "Aerobic respiration produces less ATP", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For each pair of electrons passing from NADH located inside the mitochondria to oxygen, how many ATP molecules can be generated?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In anaerobic respiration, the final electron acceptor can be", "opta": "oxygen", "optb": "nitrate", "optc": "pyruvate", "optd": "acetyl-CoA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is not produced in any of the steps of glycolysis?", "opta": "NAD+", "optb": "NADH", "optc": "ADP", "optd": "ATP", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The number of ATP molecules produced from one glucose molecule by a bacterium producing lactic acid is", "opta": "greater than producing ethanol", "optb": "lesser than producing ethanol", "optc": "approximately equal to producing ethanol", "optd": "none of these", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is the most complete definition of fermentation?", "opta": "Oxidation of glucose with organic molecules serving as electron acceptors", "optb": "Complete catabolism of glucose to CO2 and HO2", "optc": "Production of energy by substrate-level phosphorylation", "optd": "Production of ethyl alcohol from glucose", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The enzymes that catalyze the reactions of the Krebs cycle are found in which subcellular organelle of eukaryotes?", "opta": "Mitochondrion", "optb": "Chloroplast", "optc": "Ribosome", "optd": "Endoplasmic reticulum", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Fatty acids are oxidized to acetyl-CoA by which of the following pathways?", "opta": "\u03b2-oxidation", "optb": "Entner-Doudoroff", "optc": "pentose phosphate pathway", "optd": "Embden-Meyerhof pathway", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}